[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This English actress, who has starred in television commercials for Weight Watchers, played the title character Georgy in 1967s Georgy Girl.", "correct_answer": "Lynn Redgrave", "incorrect_answers": ["Elizabeth Taylor", "Julie Andrews", "Judith Dench"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where in the world can you find the dolphin known as the Boto?", "correct_answer": "South America", "incorrect_answers": ["Asia", "Australia", "North America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is the name for an octopuss tongue?", "correct_answer": "Radula", "incorrect_answers": ["Siphon", "Hemetoy", "Mantle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does dactylology study?", "correct_answer": "fingerprints", "incorrect_answers": ["rocks", "the moon", "caves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "About how much of an adult humans body is water?", "correct_answer": "60%", "incorrect_answers": ["40%", "30%", "70%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "USA is considered to be one of the most popular destinations, where thousands of immigrants come to seek asylum. Just one of these four states is similar in to USA in this respect.", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Finland", "Japan", "Portugal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are various theories for the origin of the word penguin, such the Latin word pinguis, which means what?", "correct_answer": "Fat", "incorrect_answers": ["Diver", "Upright", "Swimmer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which U.S. state is nicknamed The Golden State?", "correct_answer": "California", "incorrect_answers": ["Alaska", "Florida", "Colorado"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the gestation period of a dolphin?", "correct_answer": "Varies by species", "incorrect_answers": ["16 months", "9 months", "12 months"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jonas Salk was the 20th century American medical researcher responsible for developing the highly effective and safe oral polio vaccine.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The melody of which 1951 pop song was written by a politician who was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize?", "correct_answer": "All in the Game", "incorrect_answers": ["Lets Fall in Love", "Rock Around the Clock", "I Cant Help Falling in Love With You"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term refers to wasting away or degeneration of a muscle?", "correct_answer": "Atrophy", "incorrect_answers": ["Dystrophy", "Trophy", "Hypertrophy"]}]